webabout.org 2011-10-07

# Privacy Policy | Web About.org

I respect your privacy and I am committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at my site Webabout.org . The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

Log Files  
Like most standard Web site servers, I use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

E-mail Subscription  
If a user wishes to subscribe to my posts via e-mail (powered by Feedburner), I ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for my users’ privacy, a way to opt-out of these communications is provided.

Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. My site use cookies for tracking visitors’activity. Some of my business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, I have no access to or control over these cookies, once I have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browser’s settings section.

Google, one of our third-party advertisers, may add a cookie to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. You can choose to opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Links  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. I encourage my users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.  
Earnings Disclaimer  
I make every effort to insure that the income potential of the products, services and methods mentioned here are represented and estimated accurately. However, I cannot guarantee that you will achieve a particular level of income. You accept the risk that the earnings will differ by individual. As in any business situation, your results will vary and will be based on your individual performance, motivation and experience.

I do not make any guarantee that past earnings can be duplicated in the future nor can I guarantee your success. As with any business venture there a unknown risks which cannot be foreseen and these events may impact earnings.

If you choose to act upon the information presented here your actions should be based on your own due diligence concerning the products and concepts covered. You agree that I am not liable for any success or failure of your business that is directly or indirectly related to the use of the information, products and services presented here.  
Contact Information  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding my privacy policy, please contact me [here](http://webabout.org/about/advertise)/
